# Eli Pandolfo

Software Developer

# **Personal Info**

#### Email

elipandolfo@gmail.com

#### Phone

• (802) 498-8164

#### Github

• github.com/elip12

#### Linkedin

linkedin.com/in/eli-pandolfo

### Website

• elip12.github.io

# **Professional Skills**

### **Development Practices**

- · CI/CD
- Agile
- TDD/BDD
- RESTful API Architecture
- Relational Database Design
- · Software Testing

#### Languages

- Go
- Python
- Bash
- JavaScript & HTML
- SQL
- C & C++
- Java

#### Tools

- UNIX/Linux
- Kubernetes
- Saltstack
- AWS
- Terraform
- Postgres
- Django
- Vue

# **Certifications**

· AWS Technical Professional

# **About Me**

Infrastructure engineer at Robinhood recently graduated from UC Santa Cruz. In college I worked in computational economics and researched bacterial genomics. Intent on bridging the gap between developing cloud-native orchestration tools and operating zero-downtime infrastructure. In my down time I ski, surf, bike, backpack, and play jazz sax.

# **Experience**

### Infrastructure Engineer Robinhood, Menlo Park, CA 2020 - present

 Leverage Kubernetes to build/extend orchestration tooling and manage cloud infrastructure.

### Lab Programmer LEEPS Lab, UC Santa Cruz, CA 2017 - 2018, 2019 - 2020

- Developed real-time multiplayer economics experiments for research into markets, game theory, and decision-making.
- · Wrote Python and Bash scripts to analyze and visualize experiment data.
- Set up and maintained a public Linux production server.
- Hired, trained, and supervised four lab programmers.

# Software Engineering Intern productOps, Santa Cruz, CA 2018 - 2019

- Developed Node API and Postgres database that simplifies and streamlines the creation of AWS infrastructure, reducing startup overhead for new projects.
- Wrote end-to-end and integration tests for Angular/Node web apps, ensuring safe updates to production applications with 1000+ users.

# **Education**

### BS Computer Science UC Santa Cruz 2016 - 2020

- · GPA: 3.96
- · Regent's Scholarship
- College Scholars Program
- · Undergraduate bioinformatics & machine learning research with Linqs Lab
- Areas of focus: bioinformatics, computational economics, data wrangling & machine learning, parallel processing

### 42 Piscine 42 Silicon Valley 2017

· Four-week intensive C coding program at School 42 in Fremont, CA

# **Projects**

### Genome Wide Association Study Lings Lab, UC Santa Cruz

- Microbial GWAS program that uses statistical relational learning to predict genetic causes of bacterial phenotypes.
- Successfully identified genes in *E. coli* known to cause antibiotic resistance, outperforming a state-of-the-art method.

#### Computational Economics Experiment LEEPS Lab. UC Santa Cruz

- Multiplayer web app with Vue.js UI simulating people waiting in a queue.
- Players trade places with each other for money in real time.

## StenoScribe Android App Mobile Apps Class, UC Santa Cruz

 Mobile app for streamlining note-taking during meetings. Users can instantly share speech-to-text transcriptions, photos, and documents.